God's speaking of all states, say it's best for church from his cave, but in the heart of you.
Let us pray. Almighty God, our Heavenly Father, send down upon those who hold office in this state and city, the spirit of wisdom, charity and justice that with steadfast purpose, they may faithfully serve in their offices to promote the well-being of all people through Jesus Christ our Lord.
Amen.
Please lead us to the five of the United States of America and to the Republic for which it stands,
one nation, another God, individual, with liberty and justice for all.
Four of the Kimbutons, get the personal parisys, five, claims list.
Most of your proof.
He stepped back.
So full.
Hi.
James, hi.
Hitman.
Parker.
Hi.
Six claims list for annual concrete.
Most of your proof.
Hi.
He stepped back.
Don't don't.
Hi.
James, hi.
Hitman.
Mr. Parker.
Hi.
Seven minutes from the May 20th, May 20th, 2020, full of rigor meeting and June 3rd, 2020, full of rigor meeting.
Much of the proof.
Second.
James.
Hi.
James, hi.
Hitman.
He stepped back.
Parker.
Hi.
Please look forward to depart for meeting, historians, print years before.
I would like to say a summary of this re指 by
this.
$150,000 was budgeted for Giorty claims that current balance is 319,680 dollars in
$0.0.
If we approve this, then I'll make our balance 3.02, and 3.86, 13.
Much to approve.
Second.
Good health.
The current balance is 302, 306, 13 with the last approved claim, with a $990 approved claim.
We'll make it 301, 396, 13.
Thank you.
Mr. Jones.
Hi.
Good morning.
Dean and Gidel Stratton, Edmunds, Palmer claim for civil litigation.
We amount of $5,190.63.
Yes.
And so this is the civil litigation side for Gidel Stratton, Edmunds of Palmer claim.
So this is for extraordinary report fee for Dr. Lou, Special Master.
And this was the original from the original 300,000.
That was approved by Council on 920, 2008.
Excuse me, for the civil litigation cost.
The current balance is 24,393.
If the current invoice total is approved for $5,190.63.
That will leave us with a balance of $19,222.80 of that original 300,000.
That was set aside back in 2008.
Motion approved.
Second.
And we will go until we get somebody that can take on a project at the time.
It's nice to have five to work with because there's a lot going on.
So this agreement has two more six-month extension opportunities.
And when we extend these, they didn't change pricing or anything it was just as it was a period before.
So we recommend that the city of Miami and the Miami special utilities, except the minimum one, as presented.
I'm not sure if that.
Just a quick question.
Sure.
So does this include anything concrete or we specifically talking about roads?
It would be anything.
It's anything.
Yeah, so like we have a water-dick in concrete.
and I will have them come out if we have like solid waste as a damage concrete where you
know they put the containers that they will hire one of these vendors to kind of do
the concrete work for that too.
Okay, so it's not just robes.
It's for anything.
Okay, perfect.
Thank you.
Sure.
Second.
Jones.
All right.
Fitment.
So high.
Perfect.
All right.
Well, if engagement letter was offered to associates for accounting services
in the fiscal year 24 to 25.
So, the Crawford Associates, they work with us on many financial and accounting type services.
We've been working with them since 2009.
This is to continue to do so for the 24-25 fiscal year.
We recommend approving the engagement with Crawford Associates.
And we need your approval.
Second.
Goodman.
All right.
Thank you.
13.
Another new business of any of which represents it's opposing this agenda.
14 staff reports.
15 trustee community announcement.
16.
This meeting will be continued from council chambers to remain the staff room for the purpose of executive session.
That's the completion of agenda item number 17 of the regular meeting of the monocidic.